It is my absolute pleasure to introduce you to my amazing colleagues,
我很高兴向各位介绍我的同事
who will guide you throughout this program.
全程指导您的工作
Juno Lee is a former data scientist,
Juno Lee 是一位前数据科学家
who built neural networks for optimizing users shopping experiences.
为优化用户购物体验构建了神经网络
In this program, Juno will focus on programming tools specifically Python,
在这个程序中  Juno 将重点关注编程工具 Python
one of the most widely used programming languages in the industry.
业内最广泛使用的编程语言之一
Juan Delgado, a computational physicist with a Masters in Astronomy.
胡安 - 德尔加多 一位具有天文学大师的计算物理学家
He previously worked for NASA,
他以前曾为 NASA工作过
developing space instruments using machine learning techniques.
使用机器学习技术开发空间仪器
Juan will teach you some of the programming tools you will need to know.
胡安会教你一些你需要知道的编程工具
Mike Yee, who holds a Bachelor's of Science in mathematics and statistics,
Mike Yee 他拥有数学和统计学的理学学士学位
and received his PhD in cognitive science.
并获得了他在认知科学方面的博士学位
Mike will teach you Matplotlib,
麦克会教你 Matplotlib
the most mature Python package for data visualization.
用于数据可视化的最成熟的 Python 软件包
Jennifer Stab, holds a PhD in Computer Science,
Jennifer 穿刺 持有计算机科学博士学位
and Masters in Bio-statistics,
和生物统计学硕士
and was a university Professor of Analytics and Computer Science.
是一个大学分析和计算机科学教授
Jennifer will take you step by step through some of the labs in this nano degree.
Jennifer 会带你一步一步走过这个纳米级的实验室
The labs will be short implementations in code,
实验室在代码中是短期的
of the theory you will have learned before.
你以前学过的理论
Grant Sanderson, is a creator of the YouTube channel 3Blue1Brown,
Grant Sanderson 是 YouTube 频道 3Blue1Brown的创建者
which is dedicated to teaching math visually using a custom build animation tool.
它专用于使用定制构建动画工具直观地教学数学
He was previously a content creator at Khan Academy.
他曾是汗学院的内容创造者
Grant will bring you the beautiful visual world of linear algebra.
格兰特将为你带来线性代数的美丽视觉世界
Luis Serrano, who worked as a machine learning engineer at Google.
Luis Serrano 他在谷歌担任机器学习工程师
He holds a PhD in Mathematics from the University of Michigan,
他在密歇根大学获得数学博士学位
and a Postdoctoral Fellowship at the University of Quebec at Montreal.
蒙特利尔魁北克大学的博士后奖学金
Luis will teach you all you need to know about neural networks.
路易斯会教你需要了解神经网络的所有知识
Mat Leonard, a former Physicist,
莱纳德是前物理学家
Research Neuroscientist and Data scientist.
研究神经科学家和数据科学家
He completed his PhD and Postdoctoral
他完成了博士和博士后
Fellowship at the University of California in Berkeley.
加州大学伯克利分校的研究金
You will see Mat throughout the program in various lessons such as Pytorch.
你会在火炬手等各种课程中看到马特的整个节目
He will also help you create your first project at Udacity, in image classifier.
他还将帮助您在图像分类器的 Udacity 创建第一个项目
We are very proud of our diverse community of teachers in the school of AI,
我们为 AI 学校的多元化教师群体感到非常自豪
and can't wait to start teaching you.
迫不及待地开始教你